16reels.com 2013-06-24

# 

**We respect your privacy:**  
16reels.com helps you share information with your friends and people around you.

**Policy on IP address**  
When you login 16reels.com, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all 16reels.com visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to 16reels.com. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. 

**Policy on content**  
The content you post on this site is at your risk and we held no responsibility. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site

**Policy on Invitation**  
If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we ask you for your friend's email address. We automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. 16reels.com stores this information to send this one-time email, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [info@16reels.com](mailto:info@hiringo.com) to request for the removal of this information from our database.

**Policy on ownership**  
If the ownership of all or substantially all of the 16reels.com business, or individual business units owned by 16reels.com Pvt Ltd, were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subjected to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Website. These companies may use Personal Information, such as gender or age, and other information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites, such as time of day of the login, IP address or information about the internet service provider (ISP), in order to provide advertisements on the Website about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Confidentiality and Security**  
We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you. However, no company, including 16reels.com, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
16reels.com may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your 16reels.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our Website. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our Website. Continued use of our Website following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

**Policy on Links**  
16reels.comcontains links to sites. 16reels.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on 16reels.com.

**Contact us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: info@16reels.com
